Register of the David Starr Jordan Papers, 1794-1950
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1873-1932
  - DeKalb, Courtenay, 1917-1918 (Folder 38)
  - DePew, Pierre, 1913 (Folder 39)
  - DeSilver, Albert, 1918-1919 (Folder 40)
  - Detweiler, D. B., 1912 (Folder 41)
  - Dewa, S., 1915 (Folder 42)
  - DeWeese, Dale, 1913 (Folder 43)
  - Dewey, John, 1928 (Folder 44)
  - Dickinson, G. Lowes, 1914-1921 (Folder 45)
  - Dillingham, William P., 1921 (Folder 46)
  - Dispatch, Union, New Jersey, 1915 (Folder 47)
  - Dodge, Bayard, 1928 (Folder 48)
  - Doflein, Franz, 1914-1915 (Folder 49)
  - Dole, Charles F., 1915-1923 (Folder 50)
  - Dole, Nathan H., 1913 (Folder 51)
  - Donaldson, Robert A., 1918 (Folder 52)
  - Doubleday, Russell, 1915 (Folder 53)
  - Drahms, August, 1913 (Folder 54)
  - Dresslhuys, H. C., 1918 (Folder 55)
  - Duffus, Robert L., 1915-1918 (Folder 56)
  - Duggan, Stephen P., 1914 (Folder 57)
  - Dumas, Jacques, 1910-1914 (Folder 58)
  - Duniway, C. A., 1914-1916 (Folder 59)
  - Dunn, Robert W., 1917-1920 (Folder 60)
  - Durant, Will, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Duryea, Mrs., 1911 (Folder 2)
  - Dutton, Samuel T., 1912-1924 (Folder 3)
  - Dyburgh, Richard, 1915 (Folder 4)
  - Dye, Charity, 1915 (Folder 5)
  - Dyer, Frank, 1917-1925 (Folder 6)
  - Dyer, L. C., 1919 (Folder 7)
  - E.P. Dutton and Company, 1914-1925 (Folder 8)
  - Eagle, Joe H., 1917 (Folder 9)
  - Easley, Ralph M., 1914 (Folder 10)
  - Eastern Association on Indian Affairs, 1923 (Folder 11)
  - Eastman, Crystal, 1916-1917 (Folder 12)
  - Eckerman, C. W., 1914 (Folder 13)
  - Eckert, Ernst R., 1915-1916 (Folder 14)
  - Eckhardt, C. C., 1918 (Folder 15)
  - Eckstein, Anna B., 1910-1923 (Folder 16)
  - Eddy, J. M., 1914-1918 (Folder 17)
  - Eddy, Sherwood, 1924 (Folder 18)
  - Edwards, Arthur J., 1918 (Folder 20)
  - Edwards, E. J., Mrs., 1918 (Folder 20)
  - Edwards, Mary J., 1918 (Folder 21)
  - Eells, Charles P., 1913-1915 (Folder 22)
  - Eggert, Charles A., 1917-1919 (Folder 23)
  - Eigenmann, Carl H., 1910-1924 (Folder 24)
  - Eitel, Edmund H., 1914 (Folder 25)
  - Eldredge, Zoeth S., 1912 (Folder 26)
  - Eldridge, F. T., 1918 (Folder 27)
  - Eldridge, Seba, 1914 (Folder 28)
  - Eliot, Charles W., 1912-1924 (Folder 29)
  - Eliot, Samuel A., n.d. (Folder 30)
  - Elliman, Kenneth B., 1918-1924 (Folder 31)
  - Ely, Robert E., 1914 (Folder 32)
  - English, Frank, 1922 (Folder 33)
  - Estournelles de Constant, Baron d', 1910-1928. Includes correspondence with Paul d'Estournelles de Constant (Folder 34)
  - Eugenics Education Society, 1914 (Folder 35)
  - Evans, William, 1913 (Folder 36)
  - Evening Post, New York, 1912 (Folder 37)
  - Everett, Ray, 1911 (Folder 38)
  - Evermann, Barton W., 1916-1927 (Folder 39)
  - Expositor, 1912 (Folder 40)
  - Fahey, John H., 1914 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Fairclough, H. R., 1912-1922 (Folder 2)
  - Falconer, R. A., 1915 (Folder 3)
  - Farm and Fireside, 1914 (Folder 4)
  - Farrand, Livingston, 1922-1923 (Folder 5)
  - Farrington, Frederick E., 1914-1915 (Folder 6)
  - Faunce, W. H. P., 1915-1916 (Folder 7)
  - Fédération Abolitioniste Internationale, 1914 (Folder 8)
  - Fels, Mary, 1920 (Folder 9)
  - Ferguson, James, 1900 (Folder 10)
  - Ferguson, Maud, 1915-1916 (Folder 11)
  - Ferris, Woodbridge N., 1915-1916 (Folder 12)
  - Field, Charles K. (Carolus Ager), 1914-1923 (Folder 13)
  - Filene, Edward A., 1916-1919 (Folder 14)
  - Fisher, Edgar J., 1929 (Folder 15)
  - Fisher, Irving, 1914-1928 (Folder 16)
  - Flemming, William H., 1899 (Folder 17)
  - Fletcher, Charles R., 1923 (Folder 18)
  - Flowers, Montaville, 1923 (Folder 19)
  - Fluegel, Felix, 1918-1920 (Folder 20)
  - Ford, C. R., 1912-1913 (Folder 21)
  - Ford, Henry, 1915-1923 (Folder 22)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1921-1925 (Folder 23)
  - Foreman, F. C., 1914 (Folder 24)
  - Fortmann, Henry W., 1914 (Folder 25)
  - Foster, John W., 1897 (Folder 26)
  - Foster, William T., 1912-1920 (Folder 27)
  - Foulet, Lucien, 1909 (Folder 28)
  - Foulk, Fred B., 1915 (Folder 29)
  - Four Seas Company, 1913 (Folder 30)
  - Fourth American Peace Congress, 1913 (Folder 31)
  - Fox, S., 1914 (Folder 32)
  - Frame, James E., 1910 (Folder 33)
  - Francis, Percy, 1914 (Folder 34)
  - Francke, Kuno, 1916 (Folder 35)
  - Frannsen, B., 1915-1916 (Folder 36)
  - Frantz, Harry W., 1922-1923 (Folder 37)
  - Frazier, Joseph, 1914 (Folder 38)
  - Frear, James A., 1921 (Folder 39)
  - Freeman, 1923 (Folder 40)
  - Freeman-Gray, Maria, 1911 (Folder 41)
  - French, Burton L., 1922 (Folder 42)
  - French, W. H., 1918-1931 (Folder 43)
  - French, Will J., 1913 (Folder 44)
  - Frers, Emilio, 1914 (Folder 45)
  - Fricot, D., 1918-1920 (Folder 46)
  - Fried, Alfred H., 1910-1921 (Folder 47)
  - Friend, 1911 (Folder 48)
  - Friends of Belgium, 1922 (Folder 49)
  - Friends of Freedom for India, 1919-1920 (Folder 50)
  - Froelich, Jules, 1918-1920 (Folder 51)
  - Frye, Henry A., 1918-1919 (Folder 52)
  - Fujisawa, R., 1912 (Folder 53)
  - Fukukita, Y., 1911-1912 (Folder 54)
  - Fullerton, George S., 1914 (Folder 55)
  - Fund for the Relief of Men of Letters and Scientists of Russia, 1921 (Folder 56)
  - Furst, Clyde, 1918 (Folder 57)
  - Fyfe, Hamilton, 1922 (Folder 58)
  - Gabryz, I.(?), 1912 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Gale, Zona, 1915(?)-1928 (Folder 2)
  - Galland, Théophile, 1914 (Folder 3)
  - Gardener, Cornelius, 1913 (Folder 4)
  - Gardner, A. G., 1915 (Folder 5)
  - Garton Foundation, 1915-1916 (Folder 6)
  - Gates, F., 1914 (Folder 7)
  - Gay, Francisque, 1920 (Folder 8)
  - General Defense Committee, 1923 (Folder 9)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, 1912 (Folder 10)
  - Gerard, James W., 1923 (Folder 11)
  - German Pacifist Students' League, 1921 (Folder 12)
  - German Publication Society, 1914 (Folder 13)
  - Gilbert, Charles H., 1910 (Folder 14)
  - Gillette, Edwin, 1918-1919 (Folder 15)
  - Gillette, L. Hubert, 1913 (Folder 16)
  - Ginn, Edwin, 1909-1913 (Folder 17-21)
  - Ginn and Company, 1913-1918 (Folder 22)
  - Gisborne, Francis, 1911 (Folder 23)
  - Goethe, C., 1914-1930 (Folder 24)
  - Going, Charles B., 1918 (Folder 25)
  - Golder, Frank A., 1911-1923 (Folder 26)
  - Gompers, Samuel, 1921 (Folder 27)
  - Gordon, Robert, 1915 (Folder 28)
  - Gordy, Wilbur F., 1912 (Folder 29)
  - Gore, Thomas P., 1917 (Folder 30)
  - Gottheil, Richard, 1912-1915 (Folder 31)
  - Gotto, Sybil, 1910-1919 (Folder 32)
  - Gould, Benjamin A., 1918 (Folder 33)
  - Gould, Joseph F., 1916 (Folder 34)
  - Graham, John W., 1912-1917 (Folder 35)
  - Graham, Malbone W., Jr., 1918-1919 (Folder 36)
  - Grain Growers' Guide, 1912 (Folder 37)
  - Gray, C. de Garmo, 1914 (Folder 38)
  - Gray, R. S., 1917 (Folder 39)
  - Greater Dayton Association, 1914 (Folder 40)
  - Griffith, William, 1915 (Folder 41)
  - Guérard, Albert Léon, 1911-1928 (Folder 42-43)
  - Guild, J. M., 1914 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Gulick, Sidney L., 1913-1925 (Folder 2)
  - Gulliver, Lucile, 1912-1913 (Folder 3)
  - Haake, Herrmann, 1915 (Folder 4)
  - Haeseler, John A., 1920 (Folder 5)
  - Hale, W., 1914 (Folder 6)
  - Hall, J. J., 1915 (Folder 7)
  - Hall, James Parker, 1915 (Folder 8)
  - Hall, Prescott, 1918 (Folder 9)
  - Hallinan, Charles T., 1916-1918 (Folder 10)
  - Halsey, Francis W., 1918 (Folder 11)
  - Halstead, Albert, 1914 (Folder 12)
  - Hamilton, J. W., 1913-1929 (Folder 13-14)
  - Hammond, John P., 1914 (Folder 15)
  - Hanchett, David S., 1917 (Folder 16)
  - Hanihara, Masao, 1924 (Folder 17)
  - Hanson, David V., 1915 (Folder 18)
  - Hapgood, Norman, 1915 (Folder 19)
  - Harada, Tasuku, 1913-1920 (Folder 20)
  - Harder, A. von, 1913 (Folder 21)
  - Harding, Warren G., 1920-1922 (Folder 22)
  - Hargrove, W. C., 1915 (Folder 23)
  - Harmer, S. F., 1919 (Folder 24)
  - Harper, E. L., 1918 (Folder 25)
  - Harper, Ida Husted, 1919-1924 (Folder 26)
  - Harriman, Karl Edwin, n.d. (Folder 27)
  - Harris, C. H., 1915 (Folder 28)
  - Harris, Frank, 1918 (Folder 29)
  - Harris, John L., 1915 (Folder 30)
  - Harris, M. C., 1911-1913 (Folder 31)
  - Harsley, Fred, 1915 (Folder 32)
  - Hart, Albert Bushnell, 1919 (Folder 33)
  - Hart, Jerome A., 1907 (Folder 34)
  - Harwood, C. H., 1913 (Folder 35)
  - Harwood, M. F., 1914 (Folder 36)
  - Haskell, Henry S., 1915-1919 (Folder 37)
  - Haskell, Olcott, 1917 (Folder 38)
  - Hatch, Willard P., 1915 (Folder 39)
  - Hathaway, W. L., 1914-1915 (Folder 40)
  - Haupt, Lewis M., 1911 (Folder 41)
  - Haviland, Walter W., 1912 (Folder 42)
  - Hawk, Walter D., 1915 (Folder 43)
  - Hawley, H. B., 1914-1919 (Folder 44)
  - Haycock, A., 1914-1928 (Folder 45)
  - Hayden, Carl, 1918 (Folder 46)
  - Hayes, E. A., 1915-1917 (Folder 47)
  - Hayes, J. O. 1915 (Folder 48)
  - Heath, Carl, 1914 (Folder 49)
  - Hecht, Edel, 1915 (Folder 50)
  - Henley, Barclay, 1913 (Folder 51)
  - Henry, Melville Grenville, 1924 (Folder 52)
  - Herdmann, W. A., 1913-1915 (Folder 53)
  - Herman, Raphael, 1925-1930 (Folder 54)
  - Herringham, W. P., 1913 (Folder 55)
  - Herron, George, 1920-1923 (Folder 56)
  - Hersman, Hugh S., 1918-1920 (Folder 57)
  - Herzog, Edgar, 1918 (Folder 58)
  - Hewett, Edgar L., 1915 (Folder 59)
  - Hichborn, Franklin, 1913-1922 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Hicks, W. E., 1912 (Folder 2)
  - Higginson, Henry (?), 1912 (Folder 3)
  - Hill, Alex, 1915 (Folder 4)
  - Hill, John Wesley, 1911-1913 (Folder 5)
  - Hillman, Sidney, 1924 (Folder 6)
  - Hillquit, Morris, 1916 (Folder 7)
  - Hilton, John, 1915 (Folder 8)
  - Hinkel, J. Wolf, 1911 (Folder 9)
  - Hirst, F. W., 1911 (Folder 10)
  - Hobhouse, Emily, 1915-1924 (Folder 11)
  - Hobson, John A., 1911-1922 (Folder 12)
  - Hodges, G. Charles, 1918 (Folder 13)
  - Hodges, W. R., 1913 (Folder 14)
  - Hodgson, Caspar W., 1914-1929 (Folder 15)
  - Hohlweg, Fred, 1915 (Folder 16)
  - Holland, W. J., 1913-1923 (Folder 17)
  - Hollmann, Emil, 1914-1915 (Folder 18)
  - Holman, Alfred, 1911 (Folder 19)
  - Holman, Emile, 1919-1924 (Folder 20)
  - Holme, Ernest B., 1915-1928 (Folder 21)
  - Holmes, John Haynes, 1923-1928 (Folder 22)
  - Holmes, Rexford L., 1915 (Folder 23)
  - Holt, Byron W., 1915 (Folder 24)
  - Holt, Hamilton, 1910-1922 (Folder 25)
  - Holt, Henry, 1912-1918 (Folder 26)
  - Holt, Roland, 1910 (Folder 27)
  - Hopkins, Ernest J., 1912 (Folder 28)
  - Hooper, Franklin W., 1909 (Folder 29)
  - Hoover, Herbert Clark, 1906-1929 (Folder 30)
  - Hoover, Lou Henry, 1916-1929 (Folder 31)
  - Hopkins, Timothy, 1914-1918 (Folder 32)
  - Horn, J. S., 1912-1916 (Folder 33)
  - Houghton, Mifflin and Company, 1914 (Folder 34)
  - House, Edward M., 1915-1924 (Folder 35)
  - House, John Henry, 1914 (Folder 36)
  - Houston, Herbert S., 1916-1919 (Folder 37)
  - Howard, Clifford, 1912-1913 (Folder 38)
  - Howe, F. Stanley, 1915-1916 (Folder 39)
  - Howell, Ellen V., 1915 (Folder 40)
  - Howell, Minerva U., 1913 (Folder 41)
  - Howie, J. B., 1914-1920 (Folder 42)
  - Hoxsie, Allen P., 1914 (Folder 43)
  - Hubbell, George A., 1914 (Folder 44)
  - Huddleston, George, 1917-1927 (Folder 45)
  - Hudson, Manley O., 1913 (Folder 46)
  - Huebsch, B. W., 1920 (Folder 47)
  - Huffcut, Ernest W., 1899 (Folder 48)
  - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1921-1924 (Folder 49)
  - Hughes, Sarah Forbes, 1914 (Folder 50)
  - Hugins, Roland, 1917 (Folder 51)
  - Hull, Granville S., 1915 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Hull, William I., 1913-1919 (Folder 2)
  - Humphrey, Elizabeth Warren, n.d. (Folder 3)
  - Humphrey, H. B., 1914 (Folder 4)
  - Hunt, George W. P., 1915 (Folder 5)
  - Hunt, Harry E., 1910-1911 (Folder 6)
  - Hunt, John W., 1916 (Folder 7)
  - Hurst, C. N., 1914 (Folder 8)
  - Hurt, H. W., 1918-1919 (Folder 9)
  - Hurt, Walter, 1918 (Folder 10)
  - Huxley, Julian, 1916 (Folder 11)
  - Hyuninen, P., 1913 (Folder 12)
  - Ichihashi, Yamato, 1913-1915 (Folder 13)
  - Iijima, R. E., 1912-1913 (Folder 14)
  - Illsley, Frank P., 1916-1921 (Folder 15)
  - Immigration Restriction League, 1918 (Folder 16)
  - Indian Board of Cooperation, 1916-1922 (Folder 17)
  - Indian Defense Association, 1929 (Folder 18)
  - Indian Polytechnic Association, 1917 (Folder 19)
  - Indian Rights Association, 1928-1930 (Folder 20)
  - Indianapolis News, 1914 (Folder 21)
  - Ingersoll, William H., 1918 (Folder 22)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations, 1925-1930 (Folder 23)
  - International Association of the Friends of Peace, 1913 (Folder 24)
  - International Commission on Zoological Nomenclature, 1914 (Folder 25)
  - International Free Trade League, 1910-1918 (Folder 26)
  - International Information Bureau, 1916-1919 (Folder 27)
  - International Peace Assembly, 1913 (Folder 28)
  - International Peace Congress, 1915 (Folder 29)
  - International Peace Forum, 1911 (Folder 30)
  - International School of Peace, 1911 (Folder 31)
  - International Union of Ethical Societies, 1914 (Folder 32)
  - International Workers' Defense League, 1914 (Folder 33)
  - Irish, John P., 1920-1921 (Folder 34)
  - Irwin, Will(iam Henry), 1915-1928 (Folder 35)
  - Ishii, K., 1912 (Folder 36)
  - Ishikawa, Chiyomatsu, 1918-1924 (Folder 37)
  - Ito, Ryuzo, 1912-1914 (Folder 38)
  - Iva, Francis William, 1914 (Folder 39)
  - Japan. Consulate General (San Francisco), 1913-1929 (Folder 40)
  - Japan Chronicle, 1913 (Folder 41)
  - Japan Peace Society, 1917 (Folder 42)
  - Japanese American, 1911 (Folder 43)
  - Japanese-American Fraternity, 1913 (Folder 44)
  - Japanese Association of America, 1913-1929 (Folder 45)
  - Japanese Association of Sacramento, 1913 (Folder 46)
  - Japanese Association of Utah, 1912 (Folder 47)
  - Japanese Exclusion League of California, 1922 (Folder 48)
  - Jastrow, Joseph, 1919 (Folder 49)
  - Jastrow, Morris, 1914-1916 (Folder 50)
  - Jenkins, O. P., 1911 (Folder 51)
  - Jenks, Jeremiah W., 1915-1917 (Folder 52)
  - Jennings, Arthur E., 1914-1915 (Folder 53)
  - Jewett, William Dunbar, 1914 (Folder 54)
  - Johns, Myra Adams, 1915 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Johnson, Albert, 1923-1924 (Folder 2)
  - Johnson, Alvin S., 1913-1923 (Folder 3)
  - Johnson, Frank S., 1928 (Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Frederick A., 1925-1929 (Folder 5)
  - Johnson, Herbert B., 1911 (Folder 6)
  - Johnson, Hiram W., 1913-1927 (Folder 7)
  - Johnson, Magnus, 1924 (Folder 8)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1913 (Folder 9)
  - Johnston, W. F., 1912-1925 (Folder 10)
  - Joint Committee on Union Colleges for Women of the Orient, 1921 (Folder 11)
  - Jonah, T. F., 1916-1925 (Folder 12)
  - Jones, Edith Lloyd, 1922-1929 (Folder 13)
  - Jones, Ellis O., 1916 (Folder 14)
  - Jones, Herbert C., 1913 (Folder 15)
  - Jones, J. Kinghorn, 1915 (Folder 16)
  - Jones, Jenkyn Lloyd, 1915-1918 (Folder 17)
  - Jones, John Aubrey, 1915 (Folder 18)
  - Jones, Richard L., 1911 (Folder 19)
  - Jones, W. B., 1914 (Folder 20)
  - Jones, Walter, 1914 (Folder 21)
  - Jordan, Barbara (daughter of David Starr Jordan), 1898-1900 (Folder 22)
  - Jordan, Edith (Mrs. Gardner, daughter of David Starr Jordan), 1896-1918 (Folder 23)
  - Jordan, Eric (son of David Starr Jordan), 1898-1924 (Folder 24-27)
  - Jordan, Harold B., 1913-1918 (?) (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Jordan, Harvey E., 1912-1928 (Folder 2)
  - Jordan, Jessie Knight (second wife of David Starr Jordan)
    - 1887-1890 June (Folder 3-13)
    - 1890 September-1895 (Box 27, Folder 1-6)
    - 1896-1897 (Box 28, Folder 1-8)
    - 1898-1903 June (Box 29, Folder 1-10)
    - 1903 July-1907 (Box 30, Folder 1-8)
    - 1908-1910 June (Box 31, Folder 1-7)
    - 1910 July-December (Box 32, Folder 1-10)
    - 1911-1912 July (Box 33, Folder 1-10)
    - 1912 August-1914 July (Box 34, Folder 1-27)
    - 1914 October-1916 May (Box 35, Folder 1-20)
    - 1916 June-1917 March (Box 36, Folder 1-15)
    - 1917 April-1920 June (Box 37, Folder 1-23)
    - 1920 July-1930 (Box 38, Folder 1-21)
  - Jordan, Knight (son of David Starr Jordan), 1913-1924 (Folder 22)
  - Jordan, Mary, 1891 (Folder 23)
  - Jordan, Susan Bowen (first wife of David Starr Jordan). Includes letters to her family, 1864-1876; her obituary, 1885; and her correspondence with Jordan, 1875-1884 (Folder 24)
  - Jordan, William, 1914 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Kahn, Otto, 1918-1928 (Folder 2)
  - Kallen, H. M., 1916-1919 (Folder 3)
  - Kamada, Eikichi, 1912 (Folder 4)
  - Kammerer, Paul, 1923 (Folder 5)
  - Kasamatsu, S., 1913 (Folder 6)
  - Kato, N., 1911-1914 (Folder 7)
  - Kawakami, K.K., 1914-1915 (Folder 8)
  - Keeler, Charles, 1918 (Folder 9)
  - Kellog, Arthur P., 1919 (Folder 10)
  - Kellogg, Frank B., 1928-1929 (Folder 11)
  - Kellogg, John Harvey, 1922-1924 (Folder 12)
  - Kellogg, Paul U., 1919-1920 (Folder 13)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L., 1912-1928 (Folder 14)
  - Kennedy, A. H., 1914-1915 (Folder 15)
  - Kent, William, 1911-1921 (Folder 16)
  - Kenyon, W. C., 1915 (Folder 17)
  - Kenyon, William S., 1912 (Folder 18)
  - Keppel, F. D., 1911-1919 (Folder 19)
  - Kerr, J. Graham, 1913-1921 (Folder 20)
  - Kettner, William, 1920 (Folder 21)
  - Keyes, Henry W., 1922 (Folder 22)
  - Kiefer, Daniel, 1917-1922 (Folder 23)
  - Kilpatrick, W. H., 1899 (Folder 24)
  - Kilpatrick, Wylie, 1922 (Folder 25)
  - King, J., 1924 (Folder 26)
  - Kinghorn, Frank, 1912 (Folder 27)
  - Kingsley, Darwin P., 1915-1916 (Folder 28)
  - Kingsley, Guy R., 1917 (Folder 29)
  - Kirchwey, George W., 1915 (Folder 30)
  - Kirkpatrick, Van C., 1915-1916 (Folder 31)
  - Kishi, Junzo, 1912-1925 (Folder 32)
  - Kitchin, Claude, 1915-1916 (Folder 33)
  - Klebs, Arnold C., 1920 (Folder 34)
  - Klieforth, Alfred, 1916-1930 (Folder 35)
  - Klyce, Scudder, 1913-1923 (Folder 36)
  - Knapp, Alfred, 1913 (Folder 37)
  - Knibbs, G. H., 1915-1923 (Folder 38)
  - Knight, Austin M. (brother of Jessie Knight Jordan), 1891-1924 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Knight, Charles (brother of Jessie Knight Jordan), 1894-1930 (Folder 2)
  - Knight, J. William, 1924 (Folder 3)
  - Kobe Citizens, 1913 (Folder 4)
  - Koerner, Hermann T., 1914-1924 (Folder 5)
  - Koettgen, J., 1917-1920 (Folder 6)
  - Kokubu, S., 1911 (Folder 7)
  - Koo, V. K. Wellington, 1916 (Folder 8)
  - Koons, F. S., 1914 (Folder 9)
  - Koontz, J. A., 1914 (Folder 10)
  - Korean National Association, 1919 (Folder 11)
  - Korff, S. A., 1913-1920 (Folder 12)
  - Koscinska, M., 1912-1924 (Folder 13)
  - Kozuka, R. H., 1915 (Folder 14)
  - Kraus, Herbert, 1913-1914 (Folder 15)
  - Krehbiel, E. B., 1911-1920 (Folder 16)
  - Kroeber, A. L., 1915 (Folder 17)
  - Kuma, T., 1911-1930 (Folder 18)
  - Kunz, Josef L., 1920-1923 (Folder 19)
  - Labor Defense Council, 1922 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Labor, Socialist and Radical Movements, 1918 (Folder 2)
  - LaCroix, M. P., 1915 (Folder 3)
  - LaFollette, Robert M., 1917-1922 (Folder 4)
  - LaFontaine, H., 1910-1916 (Folder 5)
  - Laidler, Harry W., 1917 (Folder 6)
  - Lake Mohonk Conference on International Arbitration, 1910 (Folder 7)
  - Lamb, Frank H., 1923-1924 (Folder 8)
  - Lammasch, Dr., 1914-1923 (Folder 9)
  - Lamont, Thomas W., 1920-1921 (Folder 10)
  - Lane, Ralph Norman Angell, 1910-1929 (Folder 11)
  - Lange, C. L., 1910 (Folder 12)
  - Lansing, Robert, 1916-1919 (Folder 13)
  - Laselle, Mary, 1915 (Folder 14)
  - Lasker, Bruno, 1918-1928 (Folder 15)
  - Last, Grace George, 1914 (Folder 16)
  - Lathrop, Julia C., 1928 (Folder 17)
  - Law, Alexander, 1915 (Folder 18)
  - Lawlor, J. H., 1922 (Folder 19)
  - Lawrence, A. M., 1899 (Folder 20)
  - Lawrence, G. Alfred, 1926 (Folder 21)
  - Lawrence, George L., 1922 (Folder 22)
  - Lazarovich-Hrebelianovich, Princess (Eleanor Calhoun), 1919-1929 (Folder 23)
  - Lea, Clarence F., 1920-1922 (Folder 24)
  - Leach, Henry Goddard, 1924 (Folder 25)
  - League for World Peace, 1915 (Folder 26)
  - League of Free Nations, 1919-1920 (Folder 27)
  - League of Oppressed Peoples, 1919 (Folder 28)
  - League of Peace, n.d. (Folder 29)
  - League to Enforce Peace, 1915-1919 (Folder 30)
  - Ledoux, U. J., 1910-1911 (Folder 31)
  - Lenroot, Irvine L., 1921-1927 (Folder 32)
  - Lentz, Eliza, 1916 (Folder 33)
  - Lentzen, Leo James, 1927-1928 (Folder 34)
  - Leonhard, Rudolf, 1915-1916 (Folder 35)
  - Leslie Woman Suffrage Commission, Inc., 1919 (Folder 36)
  - Levermore, Charles, 1915-1926 (Folder 37)
  - Levinson, Salmon O., 1922-1930 (Folder 38)
  - Lewis, Gladys Adelina (Georges Lewys), 1928-1929 (Folder 39)
  - Libby, Frederick J., 1922-1930 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Liberator, 1920 (Folder 2)
  - Life, 1913 (Folder 3)
  - Lindauer, G. A., 1924 (Folder 4)
  - Link, Karl, 1914-1915 (Folder 5)
  - Linn, George Dana, 1915-1918 (Folder 6)
  - Lippitt, Robert R., 1915 (Folder 7)
  - Lippmann, Walter, 1918 (Folder 8)
  - Lissner, Meyer, 1911 (Folder 9)
  - Little, Brown and Company, 1912 (Folder 10)
  - Littman, Enno, 1914-1915 (Folder 11)
  - Llewellyn, K. N., 1928 (Folder 12)
  - Lochner, Louis P., 1911-1926 (Folder 13-16)
  - Lockwood, Frank C., 1914 (Folder 17)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1912 (Folder 18)
  - London, Charmian K., 1911 (Folder 19)
  - London Teachers Association, 1913 (Folder 20)
  - Long, Breckinridge, 1919 (Folder 21)
  - Loomis, Francis B., 1915 (Folder 22)
  - Losky, W., 1913 (Folder 23)
  - Lovett, Robert Morss, 1927-1928 (Folder 24)
  - Lowell, A. Lawrence, 1919 (Folder 25)
  - Lubtow, W. A., 1914-1915 (Folder 26)
  - Lucas, Frederick A., 1923 (Folder 27)
  - Luckey, G. W. A., 1918-1924 (Folder 28)
  - Lummis, Charles F., 1911-1923 (Folder 29)
  - Lund, Norman, 1912 (Folder 30)
  - Lutoslawski, W., 1914 (Folder 31)
  - Lyman, George, 1910 (Folder 32)
  - Lynch, Frederick, 1913-1930 (Folder 33)
  - Macarthur, Walter, 1920-1921 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - MacBride, Thomas, 1917-1924 (Folder 2)
  - MacDonald, A. H., 1916 (Folder 3)
  - MacDonald, J. A., 1910-1918 (Folder 4)
  - MacDonnell, John, 1914-1915 (Folder 5)
  - Mach, E. Von, 1916-1917 (Folder 6)
  - Mackay, John, 1913-1914 (Folder 7)
  - Mackie, Charles R.N., 1913-1928 (Folder 8)
  - Mackie, Ransom A., 1913 (Folder 9)
  - MacLain, J. S., 1920 (Folder 10)
  - Macleod, A. E., 1911 (Folder 11)
  - Macmillan Company, 1915-1916 (Folder 12)
  - MacMurray, J. V. A., 1924 (Folder 13)
  - Maerker-Branden, A. Paul, 1918-1927 (Folder 14)
  - "Make Hoover President" Club, 1920 (Folder 15)
  - Malloche, James, 1913-1914 (Folder 16)
  - Manly, Basil M., 1927 (Folder 17)
  - Mann, Clyde A., 1915 (Folder 18)
  - Mann, James R., 1916 (Folder 19)
  - Manus, Marjorie, 1915 (Folder 20)
  - Marburg, Theodore, 1911-1912 (Folder 21)
  - Marchant, James, 1922 (Folder 22)
  - Markham, R. H., 1913-1931 (Folder 23-24)
  - Marlborough, Duchess of, 1914 (Folder 25)
  - Marquardt, Emil, 1914-1915 (Folder 26)
  - Marshall, T. M., 1916 (Folder 27)
  - Marston, George W., 1913 (Folder 28)
  - Martin, James S., 1912-1913 (Folder 29)
  - Martin, P. A., 1912-1913 (Folder 30)
  - Martius, Margaret, 1913 (Folder 31)
  - Maryland Peace Society, 1911 (Folder 32)
  - Masaoka, Naoichi, 1913-1914 (Folder 33)
  - Masses, 1917 (Folder 34)
  - Massingham, H. W., 1911 (Folder 35)
  - Mather (?), W., 1910-1913 (Folder 36)
  - Mathie, Karl, 1918 (Folder 37)
  - Matsube, Seitara, 1918 (Folder 38)
  - Mattheeff, P., 1921-1930 (Folder 39-41)
  - Maxim, Hudson, 1916 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Maxwell, George H., 1916 (Folder 2)
  - Maxwell, Perriton, 1916-1924 (Folder 3)
  - Mayer, Alfred G., 1914 (Folder 4)
  - McAdoo, William G., 1918 (Folder 5)
  - McAlister, W. H., 1920 (Folder 6)
  - McAndrew, William, 1912 (Folder 7)
  - McArthur, Walter, 1913 (Folder 8)
  - McCartney, A. J., 1917 (Folder 9)
  - McClatchy, V. S., 1919-1925 (Folder 10)
  - McClure, S. S., 1915-1920 (Folder 11)
  - McClure's Magazine, 1919 (Folder 12)
  - McConnel, Mary, 1915 (Folder 13)
  - McCormick, Frederick, 1915 (Folder 14)
  - McCormick, Samuel B., 1915 (Folder 15)
  - McCrackin, Josephine C., 1911 (Folder 16)
  - MacDonald, J. Ramsay, 1925-1926 (Folder 17)
  - McDonald, James G., 1919-1924 (Folder 18)
  - McDonell, John, 1921 (Folder 19)
  - McDougal, W. H., 1916-1923 (Folder 20)
  - McEwan, Alexander, 1914 (Folder 21)
  - McGuire, W. B., 1914-1915 (Folder 22)
  - McHatton, John M., 1911 (Folder 23)
  - McInturff, David, 1914 (Folder 24)
  - McIntyre, J. L., 1913 (Folder 25)
  - McKinley, Jean M., 1911 (Folder 26)